[
    {

        "topic_name": "Ports",
        "prompts": [
            {
                "prompt": "What is the port number for FTP?",
                "answer": "20 for the data port and 21 for control"
            },
            {
                "prompt": "What is the port number for SSH?",
                "answer": "TCP Port 22"
            },
            {
                "prompt": "What is the port number for HTTP?",
                "answer": "TCP/UDP Port 80"
            },
            {
                "prompt": "What port number does Telnet use?",
                "answer": "TCP/UDP Port 23"
            },
            {
                "prompt": "What port does SMTP use?",
                "answer": "TCP/UDP Port 25"
            },
            {
                "prompt": "What port number does RDP use?",
                "answer": "TCP/UDP Port 3389"
            },
            {
                "prompt": "What port does DNS use?",
                "answer": "TCP/UDP Port 53"
            },
            {
                "prompt": "What port does SLP use?",
                "answer": "TCP/UDP Port 427"
            },
            {
                "prompt":"What port does SMB/CIFS use?",
                "answer": "They use TCP ports 445, unless over NetBios where they use 137-139"
            },
            {
                "prompt": "What port does SNMP use?",
                "answer": "TCP/UDP Port 161/162"
            },
            {
                "prompt": "What port does DHCP use?",
                "answer": "UDP Ports 67 and 68"
            },
            {
                "prompt": "What port does POP3 use?",
                "answer": "TCP/UDP Port 110"
            },
            {
                "prompt": "What port does IMAP use?",
                "answer": "TCP Port 143"
            },
            {
                "prompt": "What port does LDAP use?",
                "answer": "TCP/UDP Port 389"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "topic_name": "WiFi_Standards",
        "prompts": [
            {
                "prompt": "What frequency does 802.11a use?",
                "answer": "5GHz"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "topic_name": "Connectors",
        "prompts": [
            {
                "prompt": "What is a reversible USB connector type: USB2, USB-C",
                "answer": "USB-C"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "topic_name": "Virtual Machines",
        "prompts": [
            {
                "prompt": "What technology does an AMD processor need to support running a VM?",
                "answer": "AMD-V"
            }
        ]
    }
]
